The terrorists who targeted the train for Garm
merged to create an automa through
the power of the primary red gem.
Activate
[Primary Red,
Armored Knight]
Consequently, the train went out of control.
I connected myself to the massive amount of ether
in Akari to conjure a major spell and avert disaster,
Medium, Menou
-Etheric Boost-
Maintain Invoke
[Kneel before the front gate,
for its path leads to the Lord.]
but my heart is still anxious over a
bizarre sensation I felt during the trip.
I see. So you felt it too, Momo? That bizarre sensation?
Yes, I did. I see what you're thinking.
You think that was the moment when Boobalicious
used her Pure Concept to turn back time.
Akari has the Pure Concept of Time. It makes sense.
We were about to crash into the train up ahead,
which would have been a huge disaster.
And I have a hunch... that it actually happened once.
And Boobalicious turned back time?
Then you mean she can turn back
time for the entire world as well?
It seems that way.
She can turn back just her own time,
or for the entire world at will.
This time for some reason,
she chose to turn the whole world back.
But why?
Maybe she unconsciously wanted to
save the other passengers as well?
Her? You really think so?
That's how ordinary girls think.
By the way...
What about the non-ordinary girl
you got tangled up with?
You mean that crappy little princess?
Honestly, I actually thought about squishing her dead,
but I did the civil thing and shook her off my tail instead.
You should be proud of me!
What a good girl. You did a great job.
Second Class Carriage
Well then, Momo. I'll see you in Garm.
Hey, Menou?
What?
I've said this before,
but please do be careful of Miss Boobalicious there.
Second Class Carriage
Yes, I know.
There are two days until the ritual for elimination.
I have to make sure she doesn't use her
Pure Concept any more than she already has.
Later, then.
Like I said, that's not what I'm worried about...
A Pure Concept that is improperly
attached is perpetually unstable.
It grows the more it's used,
making it even more dangerous.
I have to be careful...
To make sure a tragic Human Error never happens again.
And...
To never let there be...
Another one like me from that incident.
Episode 4: The Ancient Capital Garm
I don't know what happened to me.
All I remembered was my name, "Menou."
I felt no sorrow, no fear.
I was simply there.
You've always had a flair for flashy maneuvers...
Orwell you old hag.
You haven't changed a bit yourself, Flare.
You do love acting in secrecy.
My role is different from yours.
Leave it. I'm going to look around for survivors.
I'll leave that girl in your hands.
Isn't this kind of thing your job?
You recently became a Master, didn't you?
You should take on an unfamiliar task once in a while.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm a priestess: pure, just, and strong.
Oh?
So the etheric connect doesn't bother you.
As magecraft material, you're top quality.
So? What do you want to do?
If you have a request I'll at least hear you out.
I don't have any.
Of course.
You've been blanched
both physically and mentally, after all.
As long as I'm going back that way,
I'll take care of you until the Sanctuary.
If you don't die before then,
you can do what you want after that.
Thus, I ended up traveling for a while with that woman.
And at some point,
I learned that the woman was
what was called an Executioner.
I didn't feel anything about that in particular.
Eventually, we arrived at a great continent of salt.
Can you believe it?
They say this used to be one big continent
that was home to multitudes of people.
But now everything has turned to salt,
and it's gradually dissolving into the sea.
I'm sure it won't be too far off
when it dissolves completely.
Look.
That's the Sword of Salt.
Purification embodied that turns all it pierces to salt.
A sword that can destroy the world.
The whole world could have
met the fate of this continent.
This is what a Pure Concept can do,
and the Human Error it can bring about.
This is the kind of calamity otherworlders can cause.
That's why...
The fact that your town was
wiped out is relatively benign.
I sensed in that moment that this person had made
the long journey to bring me here just to tell me that.
Just so she could give those words to a
girl who had lost all sense of emotion.
This person...
Who had looked blackish red and frightening at first...
I've decided what I want to do.
Oh?
Let's hear it.
I want to be you.
I don't understand.
You want to end up like me?
I'm an Executioner. A villain.
I thought you said you were a priestess
who is pure, just, and strong.
Are you so stupid that you don't know what sarcasm is?
You stand up to the kind of thing
that happened to my hometown.
I hate what it became, as well.
That's why I want to be like you.
If you say you're a villain, then I'll be one, too.
Why not become an ordinary priestess?
You might very well become one
that's pure, just, and strong.
Right.
You're choosing the wrong path.
You can still change your mind.
Right.
Idiot.
Can I ask what your name is?
Flare.
Actually, no.
You can call me "Master."
Yes, Master.
She took me to a convent in the depths of the Sanctuary.
There, I learned many things:
About magecraft, about the nation called Japan,
Japan
and the taboo entities that came from it.
They say our ancient civilization
once dominated the continents,
conquered the seas,
and even went beyond the skies to visit the stars.
That prosperity was made possible by making
rampant use of the otherworlders' Pure Concepts.
You can see the extent of our dependency by how their
language became the universal language of our world.
Four Major Human Errors
However...
That civilization perished due to four Human Errors.
Dragon
The Sword of Salt
Evil
The Pandemonium
Vessel
The Material Room
Star
The Starhusk
It was the result of Pure Concepts evolving out of control.
Otherworlders have no means of returning to their world.
And so, the only way to deal with
otherworlders who come to this world...
Is to kill them.
We also learned how to kill the taboo entities.
Why do we kill?
Because we are the villains, that's why!
You think it's for justice? For our faith? For the Lord?
Next!
No! There is no such vindication!
We don't get to be righteous!
We are resented, hated, and will
eventually get tossed aside.
That's the kind of villains we are!
So kill them!
Kill any and all otherworlders,
regardless of whether they are good or bad!
Speak of friendship. Whisper words of love.
Be dirty and underhanded to kill them!
Until the day comes when you die...
Kill...
And keep on killing!
Stab them? Kill them? What's wrong with everyone?!
Don't touch me!
I hate people who would tolerate the idea of murder!
There's a new girl who's two years younger
than me who I see crying a lot.
So?
I don't think she wants to kill anyone.
It's not just her.
None of the girls here want to do that.
Maybe so.
And?
So Master, make me the only bad person.
I'll kill more otherworlders than anyone else,
to make up for that girl and all the others.
So...
Make up for the others? You? Kill?
Menou, you may have value as magecraft material,
but your etheric capacity is below average.
Right.
Your physical capabilities are even lower,
although better than the worst.
Right.
Your mental abilities like memory, mental acuity,
and resourcefulness are so-so.
Just around average.
Right.
Your face isn't half bad.
You have the potential to deceive with your charms,
be it man or woman.
A step up from average.
Right.
Overall, a tad below average.
Are you really determined to be
like me with that kind of talent?
Yes, Master.
Don't make me like you. I want to be you.
A villain who has culled the most taboos
in history and is pure, just, and strong.
I see.
An awfully twisted personality has
emerged from your blanched out soul.
Then I will beat everything I know into you.
And I mean everything.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Assimilate everything I am into the blank soul of yours,
and when one day all of it is destroyed by
happiness and you still manage to survive...
That's when you'll surpass me.
Yes, Master.
Good answer.
To begin, let's do something about
your wretched etheric control
by teaching you how to use etheric camouflage.
But before that, you should do something with your hair.
There are plenty of cases where you
can manipulate people with your looks.
It's called having a sense of style.
I see. "Style," got it.
Menou, you'd better keep up.
From that day forth,
I went through a long, long period of training
to become Master Flare's successor:
Flarette.
That's right.
That's the promise I made with Master Flare.
I have to kill more otherworlders than anyone,
as many as I possibly can.
That's my job.
That was a nice nap!
It's afternoon already, sleepyhead.
What? Really?
Look! We can see it already.
Is that Garm?
Wow!
Yes, that's where the ceremonial hall is
where we can send you back home.
That's our destination.
What a pretty city!
Isn't it? Garm is famous for its scenic beauty.
Menou, Menou! I want to go see the sights here!
Oh, together with you, of course!
I think fun things are even better with two people!
Sure. But first, there's a place I need to visit.
It's a date, okay? You'd better keep your promise!
Fine, fine.
There?! Is that castle where we're going?!
Sorry, but no.
That's the former royal palace.
It's Noblesse territory where the royalty,
nobility and knights are.
I have business over that way.
That's the cathedral, a sacred place for us Faust.
Didn't you say the Faust and
the Noblesse don't get along?
But they're next to each other?
It's a historic city, so I'm sure there are reasons for that.
Anyway, that's where we'll find the
hall we're looking for, apparently.
Oooh. Woow!
Sooo pretty...
Stop talking. You sound like an idiot, Akari.
You make some pretty biting
comments sometimes, Menou.
Only because you keep acting like a dummy.
Menou, you're so cold! I'm going home soon, you know?!
But it really is something, isn't it?
I've never actually been in this cathedral before,
but it's breathtaking.
Resplendent, elaborate, and it's even
adorned with multiple magecraft crests.
Protection
Multiple-Wall
Sanctum Barrier
Is that so amazing?
It enhances the outer wall as a protective barrier,
but also has a barrier that functions internally.
It's a highly efficient setup.
Of course.
Only a select few have the skill to activate it effectively.
Like Archbishop Orwell.
Well, thank you for your kind words, Miss Menou.
Archbishop Orwell!
Please forgive me for not noticing.
No need to be so formal.
I'm so glad we finally get to meet, Miss Menou.
I heard there was trouble on the train?
Yes. I'm sorry for the worry.
I'm just glad you're all right.
Then you must be...
M-my name is Akari Tokitou!
Nice to meet you, I'm Orwell.
I've heard about your situation.
How awful it must have been to be
suddenly summoned to another world!
No, it honestly wasn't anything!
Rest assured...
The preparations for the ritual that will
send you home are coming along just fine.
We should be able to hold it two days from now, at noon.
A-ah! I do appreciate it so deeply much!
Akari! Your words are coming out all wrong!
By the way, what do you intend to do
once the ritual is over, Miss Menou?
If you're planning to take the
Pilgrimage Route along the border,
the Church can cover your pilgrimage expenses.
What, really?! Thank you very much!
But, if you would like to be helpful in return,
I'd like to ask you a favor.
What is it?
Do you remember the incidents happening
in Garm I told you about?
Yes. I believe you said that a series of
young women have gone missing.
Exactly, so...
I was hoping you could look
into it until the ritual is ready.
Do you think I'll be of any help?
I need a different perspective on it.
If you don't end up finding anything, that's fine.
All right. If you say so, Archbishop.
Thank you. I'm counting on you, Miss Menou.
Wow, what a nice room!
The Archbishop must have pulled some strings for us.
Akari?
What?
Are you mad about something?
That's right, I'm mad.
Um...
Why?
We promised it would be a date!
You said we would go sight-seeing together,
but then you went and promised that
archbishop lady something else!
You mean the investigation? But that-
In return, you're getting money for
some pilgrimage thingy, aren't you?
Of course that's more important to you.
Listen, Akari-
I know!
To you, that lady's an important
person you respect, right?
But me, I'm just some stranger passing
by who's going to be gone soon!
I didn't mean it like that-
Hmph! Whatever!
I'm going to take a bath!
The day after tomorrow, Akari will be...
Jeez! Stupid Menou!
I'm the stupid one...
Menou? Did you want me?
Hmm, a series of disappearances, huh?
You think human trafficking is
rampant in this city or something?
Apparently not. They've investigated that already.
Then maybe some heretic is collecting
material to summon a demon?
It does feel like an Original Sin
might be involved somehow.
I want you to look into that side of things.
Hmm. Well, I don't mind helping out, of course.
While I'm investigating this, what will you be doing?
Uh?! Well...
Akari and I are uh... going sight-seeing...
But of course you are!
You can't bring that useless set of boobs
along with you to do any kind of investigation!
Uhhh, that's right. I'm glad you understand...
Momo...
I love you so much that I'll do anything you ask me to do.
Thank you, Momo.
I'll get this done in no time, just you wait!
Hey, Momo!
The primary red gems that those
terrorists were told to swallow...
They were probably provided by
someone with magecraft expertise.
The terrorists hinted that they could get
away as long as they got to Garm.
If whoever conspired with them is in Garm,
maybe that's where the red gems came from as well.
And that person might be one of
the Noblesse here in the city...
I take it?
I'm glad you're quick on the uptake.
Exactly. So be careful.
All right. I've got it, ma'am!
I always force the messy stuff on her plate.
Akari...
What are you doing out here dressed like that?
I'm so sorry, Menou!
I know your work as a priestess is really important to you,
and I was insensitive.
Really, I'm sorry. I'll go sight-seeing by myself.
Good luck with the job you have to do.
"Fun things are even better with two people," right?
Of course, if you'd rather go alone, that's fine too.
Of course not! I want to go with you, Menou!
I swear. I swear!
Oh, Menou!
Okay, okay, I get it.
I get it so you can let go of me, Akari.
Uh, Akari. Your towel.
Flarette...
That girl has the potential now...
Wouldn't you agree, Flare?
Oh, my lower back hurts.
Next Episode
Goodbye
Next episode: Goodbye.